[Music]
Hello there. It's been a while. A lot
has changed at the cottage. Where do I
even begin? I suppose with the fact that
I have a soon-to-be toddler. I have been
navigating the raw, overwhelming,
painful, and fascinating journey of
metrics. Day by day, I fall more in
love. Day by day, I discover new things
about myself. I have grieved the
temporary loss of certain hobbies that I
don't have time for anymore. I've found
joy in discovering new interests and
sharing a vibrant world with a curious
little soul. Sometimes I've desperately
wanted to be alone and in a quiet place.
On chilly mornings, I cannot imagine
anywhere better to be than cuddled up
with a tiny fairy and hear them laugh.
Many shifting contradictory emotions
that remind me of just how human I am.
We contain multitudes indeed.
[Music]
I've been working at my little
bookstore, piecing together a sort of
eclectic career. I still make videos for
Patreon, which has become a place of
connection and joy for me. I sell my
poetry books on Etsy. I take work
locally as a photographer. And thanks to
the kindness of so many kindred spirits,
I found a sense of stability during this
new life away from
YouTube. But things are ever changing.
That I know. And I've accepted that
someday, no doubt, things will once
again shift. So, cheers to the journey.
and to staying curious and
hopeful. I know for many including
myself, this year has felt uncertain and
scary at times. And that is why I wanted
to share a little update with you simply
to send you some love. I encourage you
to be bold and thrive in an imperfect
world and find small ways to shine your
light, your goodness, your heart song.
And just like that, you've made the
world a better
[Music]
place. I suppose all this means that I'm
on a winding path. Where it will lead
someday doesn't really matter. Only that
I continue along, stumbling and skipping
and wandering here and there. Once we
begin to explore the landscape of the
soul, life is never the same again.
Neither is it boring. It just keeps
evolving. I have spent enough of my life
preparing to live. I don't want to waste
one more moment anywhere but
here. Sending all my
love. Goodbye.